Hello friends, regarding Step Towards Investment
YouTube2, its share has
given a closing today at 268 p.m. with a rise of 7.93 p.m. i.e., with a rise of approximately 75%. So
SRM Contractors Limited has received a
new project from the National Highway
Authority of India i.e.
NHAI worth Rs. 171 crore. So SRM
Contractors Limited has got a new project from the
National Highway Authority of India,
which is worth
Rs. 171 crore and due to this update,
we saw a rise of approximately 8 p.m. in the share price of SRM Contractors Limited today. Now let's
talk about NBCC India Limited,
its share has
given a closing today at 17.45 p.m. with a rise of 7.41 p.m. i.e., with a rise of approximately 75%. So NBCC
India Limited company secured order worth Rs.
11 crore. So let's understand this update in a little detail.
NBCC India Limited's
subsidiary company
HSCC India has been given a contract by the Government of
Maharashtra to build the
New Government Medical College in Buldhana.  An
order worth Rs 45 crore has been received for construction of 411.11 crore. Due to this update,
today
we saw a rise of about 75% in the share price of NBCC India Limited.
Now let's talk about Bharat Heavy
Electricals Limited, that is,
BHEL. Its shares
closed today at Rs 323.60 with a rise of Rs 1.99, that is, with a rise of about 2%. Bharat Heavy
Electricals Limited is bagging Rs 10,000
crore order from Damodar Valley Corporation.
So let's understand this update in a little detail. So
friends, this update came last week on
Friday after the market closed
and this update was that Bharat Heavy
Electricals Limited has
received an order worth Rs 10,000 crore from Damodar Valley Corporation to set up a 1600 MW
thermal power
station in Koderma district of Jharkhand state.
Due to this update, today we saw a rise of 2%
in the share price of Bharat Heavy Electricals Limited.
Now let's talk
about Karnataka Bank Limited.
Its stock closed at 23.45 today
with a gain of 6.82 per cent.
Karnataka Bank
Limited has partnered
with ICICI Lombard General Insurance
to offer health
insurance, motor insurance, travel
insurance, and home insurance to enhance
customer benefits. Due to this update,
we saw a rise of about 7 per cent in the share price of Karnataka Bank Limited today. Now let's
talk about L&T, its
stock closed at 3775 today with a gain of 2.58 per cent.
L&T has
received multiple orders for its power transmission and distribution business, the
value of which is
in the range of Rs 2000-500 crore to Rs 5000 crore.
Due to this update, we saw a rise of more than 1 per cent in the share price of L&T today.
Now let's talk
about JSW Energy Limited, its stock
closed at 69150 today with a decline of 30 per cent. JSW
Energy  Subsidiary gets letter of intent to
set up 192 MW grid connected
hybrid power project in Gujarat. So let's
understand this update in a little detail.
JSW Neo Energy, the owned subsidiary company of JSW Energy Limited, has
received a letter of intent from Gujarat Urja Vikas Nigam Limited to set up a 192 MW grid connected hybrid power project in Gujarat. So
friends, if you found this video informative,
then like this video and
subscribe to the channel.